um just a quick video lets you know that
I do now have a Reddit I have a
subreddit uh where you can go in here
and have persistent conversations about
these videos um this is a place to go if
you have questions uh if you want to
know more this is where I'm going to be
reading and interacting because it's
persistent and it's not going to go away
it's not like a discord's going to
decide to clear out the cash um so this
is the place to go if you want me to
answer you uh I prefer you put your
YouTube comments here instead if you
have a Reddit account if you I will try
to read as many of the YouTube comments
as I can from now on but uh this is
really the better place to go I I might
not like Reddit the Reddit community in
general doesn't matter um this is
clearly the best place to have a
threaded conversation about each of
these videos so please come here and and
you know let me know join the RBX Rob
Community uh here on reden thank you